http://www.directhomemedical.com/directhomemedical-privacy-policy-terms-of-use.html

About Us
Why Shop with Us?
Mail: 142 Lowell Road, Suite 17-392 Hudson, NH 03051
More...
html_profile
product_display DirectHomeMedical Customer Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
Code: directhomemedical-privacy-policy-terms-of-use
Price:
$0.00
Quantity in Basket:
None
RETURN & EXCHANGE POLICIESPlease also read our Return & Exchange Policies, which govern all orders and products sold through DirectHomeMedical.com.
COMMUNICATING WITH USWhen you visit DirectHomeMedical.com, call us, live chat us, send us a letter or e-mail us, you are communicating with us. By doing so, you consent to receive communications from us.
SALES & PROMOTIONSAt times throughout the year DirectHomeMedical may advertise special pricing or discounts on selected products. Information on sales and promotions is distributed through our email newsletter, directly on our site and/or on third party websites. All sales and promotions are offered at the sole discretion of DirectHomeMedical and can be withdrawn at any time.
PRICE QUOTESAs a customer you may at any time request special pricing on any item we sell. If you are provided with a price quote based on such a request that quote is only valid for you the requestor. Unless otherwise specified, price quotes cannot be shared or forwarded to other customers or companies; and doing so will immediately invalidate the price quote.
COPYRIGHT NOTICEAll content included on this site, such as text, descriptions, graphics, logos, icons, and images, is the property of DirectHomeMedical.com or its suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws.
TRADEMARKSDirectHomeMedical.com, DirectHomeMedical and other DirectHomeMedical icons, graphics, logos, button designs, and service names are trademarks or trade dress of DirectHomeMedical or its parent companies. DirectHomeMedical's trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not DirectHomeMedical.com's, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits DirectHomeMedical. All other trademarks, not owned by DirectHomeMedical.com, that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, and are used with permission.
THE PRODUCTS WE SELLDirectHomeMedical.com offers products from a selection of manufacturers and vendors. By purchasing products through our website you agree that all services related to said products -- including ordering, sale, delivery, setup and instruction will be performed by DirectHomeMedical.com independently of the manufacturer. This does not effect manufacturer's warranties or warranty repairs which will be undertaken in accordance with each individual manufacturer's policies.
PRESCRIPTION ITEMSDirectHomeMedical will inform you, both on the product page before purchase and via email after purchase, when a prescription is required for a specific item. If a prescription is required we will verify, prior to the completion of sale, the prescription by a physician licensed to practice in the United States.
LICENSE AND SITE ACCESSDirectHomeMedical.com grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site. You are not given permission to download (other than page caching) or modify this site, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of DirectHomeMedical.com. This site, or any portion of it, may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent DirectHomeMedical.com
YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO USAt DirectHomeMedical.com we know that you care how your personal information is used and shared. We appreciate your business and the trust that you place in us, our products and our services and we want you to understand our policies with regards to the information we gather when you visit our site or place an order with us.
This Privacy Policy describes how we gather and use the information you submit. By visiting our site and purchasing our products, you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.
Does DirectHomeMedical.com Sell Customer Information to Other Companies?DirectHomeMedical.com will never sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose customer information to third parties for their marketing or commercial purposes.
What Personal Information Does DirectHomeMedical.com Gather About Customers?We receive and store information (such as your name, e-mail address, billing information, phone numbers, etc.) you enter on our Web site or provide to us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our store, and communicating with you.
What Are Cookies and Do You Use Them at DirectHomeMedical.com?DirectHomeMedical uses technologies, such as cookies and pixels, to keep track of visitor activities, functionality and usage patterns on our website. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. We, and our third party partners, use cookies to enhance your shopping experience through personalized product recommendations, user accounts and off site promotions.
Our cookies only collect information that does not personally or directly identify you. In most cases your browser will allow you to block or remove our cookies however this may impact site performance and/or limit your ability to access specific areas and functionalities. You can learn more about targeted advertising, and opt out options, from the Digital Advertising Alliance or the Network Advertising Initiative.
Does DirectHomeMedical.com Share Information it Receives with Other Companies?The information you provide us is an important part of what makes us successful. When you provide us with information we consider it our responsibility to protect that information and use it to provide the best possible service to you. The paragraphs below describe how your information may be shared and transferred:
Orders & Requests: When fulfilling an order or request we may and will share your information with agents and other companies whom we employ to perform specific functions -- such as processing credit card payments, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, providing search results, etc. -- on our behalf. These agents and other companies will have access to personal information needed to perform their functions for us, but may not use it for purposes other than those specifically assigned.
Transfers of Business: As we continue to develop our company we may buy or sell portions or our business, other stores or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy such as this one.
Legal Issues: We will release customer information to the proper authorities if we believe such a release is required to comply with the law or law enforcement agencies; or when the release of such information is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of DirectHomeMedical.com, its employees, or others.
This may include the exchange of information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing customer information to third parties for commercial purposes.
Promotions: We may at our discretion, reproduce comments or opinions submitted to us by our customers for promotional purposes directly related to DirectHomeMedical and our online businesses. If you would prefer that your comments not be used in our promotional materials please submit your preference to us using the contact information elsewhere on this site. In addition we may share non-personally identifiable information via cookies as described elsewhere in this policy.
Other Reasons: Other than as set out in the previous paragraphs we will not share the information you submit with any third parties without your prior consent.
How Secure Is the Information You Submit to DirectHomeMedical.com?When you submit information to DirectHomeMedical.com or one of our affiliates we work to protect the security of that information during transmission using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. SSL software encrypts information you input so that it is protected throughout the transmission process.
When confirming your order we will only reveal the last four or five digits of your credit card number in order to confirm the transaction. Using SSL software we will also transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company for order processing.
In addition, we encourage you to protect your information against unauthorized access. Be sure to sign of of any open accounts when you have completed your use of the internet and our site.
Do I Have to Share Information With You?You have no obligation to share any information with DirectHomeMedical.com and you can always choose not to provide information we request; however in choosing not to provide requested information you may make it impossible for us to fulfill your order. In such cases we will let you know prior to completing your order of any problems that might be caused if information is witheld.
ChildrenDirectHomeMedical.com does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use DirectHomeMedical.com only under the supervision of a parent or guardian.
QuestionsWe hope this Privacy Policy has helped you but if you still have questions please contact us using the information elsewhere on this site.
Changes to this DocumentDirectHomeMedical.com reserves the right to make changes to our site, policies, and this Privacy Policy at any time.
These Conditions of Use & Privacy Policy were last updated: November 27, 2014
global_footer
global_template-cssui-global-footer-item.htm.html
Sleep Therapy
CPAP & BiPAP Masks
CPAP & BiPAP Machines
Parts & Accessories
Oxygen Therapy
Oxygen Concentrators
Contact Us
Receive Site News, Discounts, Coupons & Product Updates.
Credit Card Online Payments
All DirectHomeMedical offers online support through our website, live chat and toll free support during normal business hours, and email support 24-hours a day. Please contact us if you have any questions about our services or the products we sell. DirectHomeMedical.com is authorized and approved, by the manufacturers we represent, to sell and ship products to end-users residing in the United States, not to other third parties or businesses. A prescription is required for the purchase of certain products on this site. All products offered are sourced directly from the original equipment manufacturers or their representatives. PROPOSITION 65 WARNING: Some products on this site may contain a chemical known to the State of California to cause cancer, birth defects or other reproductive harm. COPYRIGHTS: Selected product images and descriptions used throughout this site are used with the permission of the copyright holders. All ResMed Product Images © ResMed. All Philips Respironics Product Images © Philips Respironics. All Fisher & Paykel Healthcare Product Images © Fisher & Paykel Healthcare. Site Design & Content Copyright © 2004-2018 DirectHomeMedical. Respironics recommends that new patients purchase their devices, masks and initial accessories from a homecare company that can provide an individualized patient equipment set-up, clinical and after-sale support, and a program to assist patients with therapy success. All products and services advertised on this site are provided by DirectHomeMedical.com or its designates. DirectHomeMedical occasionally offers discounts via coupon code. Coupon codes cannot be combined and there is a limit of one coupon per order. DISCLAIMER: Information on this website is informational only and should not replace the advice of a physician.
